<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<terms xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<term>
		<id>1</id>
		<title>Reactivate Household</title>
		<hint>Reactivate Household</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.7: For a given Household ID, references to a particular device are deleted from the headend, causing the headend to be unresponsive to license requests.</meaning>
		<group>BUS and User</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>2</id>
		<title>Remove Device from Household</title>
		<hint>Remove Device from Household</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.4: Cause a suspended Household ID to become active again, enabling system activity using that household ID and use of associated database records such as login data (username, password), cryptographic data, and device data (iOS, Android, PC, MAC).</meaning>
		<group>BUS and User</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>3</id>
		<title>Delete Household</title>
		<hint>Delete Household</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.2: Delete a Household ID from the system and bar access to its associated database records. Upon completion, the user’s device can no longer access database records needed for login (username, password), cryptographic functions, or TV rendering.</meaning>
		<group>BUS and User</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>4</id>
		<title>Query Household Information</title>
		<hint>Query Household Information</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.5: A query returns data related to a given Household ID’s associated database records such as login data (username, password) and device data (iOS, Android, PC, MAC). Note that cryptographic data cannot be returned in answer to this query.</meaning>
		<group>BUS and User</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>5</id>
		<title>Add Offer to Linear Channel</title>
		<hint>Add Offer to Linear Channel</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.10: A set of offer properties are allocated an offer ID and associated with a business scenario. Once complete, a linear channel can be associated to this offer ID, and the system can then support authorization of a household to the offer. This use case is part of system setup and does not occur in every day operation.</meaning>
		<group>BUS and User</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>6</id>
		<title>Suspend Household</title>
		<hint>Suspend Household</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.3: A Household ID is flagged as suspended. A user’s device with a suspended household ID can no longer utilize its associated database records such as login data (username, password), cryptographic data, and device data (iOS, Android, PC, MAC).</meaning>
		<group>BUS and User</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>7</id>
		<title>Authorize Household</title>
		<hint>Authorize Household</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.6: A household ID is flagged as authorized. This flag updates associated database records in such a way that a device associated with the household ID can render content upon license request.</meaning>
		<group>BUS and User</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>8</id>
		<title>Create Household</title>
		<hint>Create Household</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.1: Create a Household ID and associated database records required when a user’s device requests login (username, password), cryptographic data, or the ability to render TV (iOS, Android, PC, MAC).</meaning>
		<group>BUS and User</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>9</id>
		<title>Add Linear Channel</title>
		<hint>Add Linear Channel</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.8: A new channel of streaming TV is configured using the data master UIs, adding transport stream ID, service ID and URL. The SMC is configured with encoder’s multicast and AC Blob. ECM components are updated with the AC as needed.  </meaning>
		<group>Content</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>10</id>
		<title>Ingest Linear Schedule</title>
		<hint>Ingest Linear Schedule</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.9: Upload an XTI-formatted file describing the linear schedule to the CI component which updates the data masters as needed. The schedule is then cached by the TWC and made available to user’s devices.</meaning>
		<group>Catalog</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>11</id>
		<title>Upload Content to CDN</title>
		<hint>Upload Content to CDN</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.13, 3.2.14, 3.2.15: To upload content the origin server propagates files to the CDN including manifest files and video chunk TS files.</meaning>
		<group>Catalog</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>12</id>
		<title>Linear Content Delivery</title>
		<hint>Linear Content Delivery</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.11: The SSP-IP, using a CW from the ECMS, encrypts the linear TV content, packages it, and delivers each separate chunk as an independent file to the origin server, stored in a folder labeled as per bitrate.</meaning>
		<group>Catalog</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>13</id>
		<title>Show Linear Grid</title>
		<hint>Show Linear Grid</hint>
		<meaning>3.4.2: Content selection for linear playback is made available to the viewer in such a way as to enable its rendering in a grid as follows: Navigator UI client queries the CMDC for each day, generates the grid, and downloads the Channel logos.</meaning>
		<group>Content</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>14</id>
		<title>Ingest and Deliver VOD Content</title>
		<hint>Ingest and Deliver VOD Content</hint>
		<meaning>3.2.12: An ADI-formatted file is uploaded to the CMS Lite initiating a workflow of many steps where the VOD asset is assigned the correct offer data, allocated cryptographic keys, transcoded, its meta-data entered into the catalog, encrypted, packaged into chunks, and chunks and channel manifests are uploaded to the CDN.</meaning>
		<group>Content</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>15</id>
		<title>Show VOD, Catch-up Catalog</title>
		<hint>Show VOD, Catch-up Catalog</hint>
		<meaning>3.4.2: VOD/Catch-up Content Selection for VOD playback is made available to the viewer: Navigator UI client queries the CMDC for each day, generates the grid, and downloads the posters.</meaning>
		<group>Catalog</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>16</id>
		<title>Register Device</title>
		<hint>Register Device</hint>
		<meaning>3.3.1: A user’s device performs cryptographic sequences as needed to enable secure communication, authenticate, initialize secure libraries on the client (SDLL, DNX), and associate the device with its set of headend-hosted database records.</meaning>
		<group>DRM and CA</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>17</id>
		<title>In-App TVOD Purchase</title>
		<hint>In-App TVOD Purchase</hint>
		<meaning>TBD</meaning>
		<group>DRM and CA</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>18</id>
		<title>Play VOD ABR Content</title>
		<hint>Play VOD ABR Content</hint>
		<meaning>3.3.7: The user’s device reads the catalog asset URL and retrieves the relevant manifest that contains chunked video file URLs. The client uses ABR algorithms to manage the download bandwidth; retrieved files are then processed by the client’s cryptographic software which, using the license, can render the video.</meaning>
		<group>DRM and CA</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>19</id>
		<title>Boot Device</title>
		<hint>Boot Device</hint>
		<meaning>3.3.2: A user’s device refreshes some cryptographic data as needed to renew secure communication and receive any updates (authorizations) from certain headend-hosted database records. Note that secure libraries on the client (SDLL, DNX) are not affected.</meaning>
		<group>DRM and CA</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>20</id>
		<title>Get VOD License</title>
		<hint>Get VOD License</hint>
		<meaning>3.3.5: The user’s device uses cryptographic sequences to securely connect and submit VOD asset metadata. The system parses the supplied metadata, verifies the authorizations against database records associated with the household ID and, if there is a match, returns a valid license.</meaning>
		<group>DRM and CA</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>21</id>
		<title>Concurrency Control</title>
		<hint>Concurrency Control</hint>
		<meaning>3.3.9: The user’s device uses cryptographic data to request a concurrency ticket from the concurrency server. The server verifies that there is an empty slot for the device’s household, allocates it to this household, and returns the ticket.</meaning>
		<group>DRM and CA</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>22</id>
		<title>Get Linear License</title>
		<hint>Get Linear License</hint>
		<meaning>3.3.3: The user’s device uses cryptographic sequences to securely connect, supply relevant authorization data, and request a valid license for a given linear asset. The system inspects the user-sent data and, if OK, returns a license for the asset.</meaning>
		<group>DRM and CA</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>23</id>
		<title>Play Linear ABR Content</title>
		<hint>Play Linear ABR Content</hint>
		<meaning>3.3.6: The user’s device reads the asset URL from the catalog and retrieves the relevant manifest. The client then discovers in the manifest the URLs of the chunked video files and uses ABR algorithms to manage the download bandwidth. The retrieved files are then processed by the client’s cryptographic software which, using the license, can render the video.</meaning>
		<group>DRM and CA</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>24</id>
		<title>Pause and Resume</title>
		<hint>Pause and Resume</hint>
		<meaning>3.3.8: The end-user can command her device to pause and/or resume rendering video. </meaning>
		<group>Client</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>25</id>
		<title>Tune to Channel</title>
		<hint>Tune to Channel</hint>
		<meaning>3.3.10: A user interacts with the Navigator UI in such a way as to enable the client to get the manifests and chunks relating to a particular channel.</meaning>
		<group>Client</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>26</id>
		<title>Show Linear Grid</title>
		<hint>Show Linear Grid</hint>
		<meaning>3.4.2: A user interacts with the Navigator UI in such a way as to enable it to query the CMDC for each day and generate the grid.</meaning>
		<group>Client</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>27</id>
		<title>Show Banner</title>
		<hint>Show Banner</hint>
		<meaning>3.4.5: A user interacts with the Navigator UI in such a way as to enable it to show a banner.</meaning>
		<group>Client</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>28</id>
		<title>Select VOD Asset with Asset ID</title>
		<hint>Select VOD Asset with Asset ID</hint>
		<meaning>3.3.11: A user interacts with the Navigator UI in such a way as to enable the client to get a VOD asset’s ID and select a VOD asset</meaning>
		<group>Client</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>29</id>
		<title>Show VOD/Catch-up Catalog</title>
		<hint>Show VOD/Catch-up Catalog</hint>
		<meaning>3.4.3: A user interacts with the Navigator UI in such a way as to enable the client to show the VOD catalog. Catch-up catalog is TBD in Infintie TV.</meaning>
		<group>Client</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>30</id>
		<title>Search for Content</title>
		<hint>Search for Content</hint>
		<meaning>3.4.6: A user interacts with the Navigator UI in such a way as to enable the client to send queries to the TWC via the CMDCv2 and thus discover content.</meaning>
		<group>Client</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>31</id>
		<title>Navigator Application Start up</title>
		<hint>Navigator Application Start up</hint>
		<meaning>3.4.1: A user interacts with her device in such a way as to start-up the Navigator UI. The application then instantiates itself for operation.</meaning>
		<group>Client</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>32</id>
		<title>Show Content Details</title>
		<hint>Show Content Details</hint>
		<meaning>3.4.4: A user interacts with the Navigator UI in such a way as to reveal the details associated with an asset.</meaning>
		<group>Client</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
	<term>
		<id>33</id>
		<title>Manage Settings</title>
		<hint>Manage Settings</hint>
		<meaning>3.4.7: A user interacts with his device in such a way as to set parameters that are used by the Navigator UI and client.</meaning>
		<group>Client</group>
		<type>use case</type>
		<source>NDS</source>
	</term>
</terms>